http://www.centralheightschurch.com/privacypolicy

unexpected - the story of jonah : nov - dec 2018
words that change your world - the Lord's prayer : sept - nov 2018
give policies and terms
Your privacy is important to us. This policy covers all information entered on any centralheights.ca webpage. Please check back as this policy may be updated from occasionally with minor changes. Please contact us regarding any questions.
Registration and login is not required on most Central Heights Church webpages, but the following information may be collected from our website depending on the services:
In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.
Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website. Cookies are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website. Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.
Do We Share Your Information?
Email addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to third parties. Non-personal user and traffic data is accessible to our web teams, who work to improve your experiences with our website. Personal information is collected only for ministry purposes.
Any data collected during the giving process is accessible by our financial team for recordkeeping and tax receipting purposes. Central Heights Church does not share donor information with any other parties.
Central Heights Church does not share your personal information with other institutions. We may however share your personal information only if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms Of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Central Heights Church, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
Our Security Measures
To safeguard your personal information and protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data, we implement SSL security wherever personal information is input such as giving pages, and we do not store local data on our machines related to credit card numbers or personal identification numbers. Access to any data is only granted to those personnel, staff, and contractors that are either directly involved in using the required data or using it to improve our sites. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
Central Heights Church reserves the right to change or update this Policy at any time.
